

# KRYSTIAN MUSZYŃSKI

### About me

I'm an open, kind, team spirit person who loves programming and gaining new experiences. I found new passion in it and would like to associate my future with it. Besides that my other passion are cars.

My portfolio: https://vnill125.github.io/portfolio/

# **Projects**

#### AutoCar

Django web application based on Polish site OtoMoto where you can list and buy cars. Application contains user autentication, login, register form. Allow users to list new cars, upload multiple images, chat between two users. View and edit our orders. Filter and sort cars.

#### **Technology Stack**

Python, JavaScript, Django, HTML, CSS

https://github.com/Vnill125/AutoCar

## **Marketplace Website**

Marketplace website where user can list they products for sell. Application allows user to list new products, edit them, browse items and chat with other users to discuse.

### **Technology Stack**

Python, Django, Tailwind, HTML, CSS

https://github.com/Vnill125/Car-rental-website

### Full Stack Notes

Simple full stack web application where each user can create, update and delete notes.

#### **Technology Stack**

Python, Django Rest Framework, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS

https://github.com/Vnill125/Notes

## **Experience**

## Warehouseman

Moraj / Żory 03.2023 - Currently

- loading of lorries
- unloading of lorries
- unloading of containers
- execution of orders
- unloading of goods

Carbotex / Jastrzębie-Zdrój

**Logistics Specialist** 

03.2023 - 07.2023

- working in Optima software, - managing the fleet of vehicles,
- werhouse, containers advising,
- reciving goods on stock,
- booking containers,
- valuation of transports,
- creation documents

#### Salesman

JYSK / Zory 03.2023 - 07.2023

- customer service,
- changing the concept of the store,
- store inventory,
- taking complaints,
- taking delivery,

# +48 660 429 213

- kris125132@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Vnill125
- Żory, Poland

## **SKILLS**

Python

Django + DRF

JavaScript

React

HTML/CSS

**TAILWIND** 

PostgreSQL

SOL

# **EDUCATION**

2023 - Present

Computer science Górnośląska Wyższa Szkoła

Handlowa 2016 - 2020

**Technical Logistics** Zespół Szkół nr.2 im. ks. prof. Józefa Tischnera

Polish - Native

English

# **LANGUAGE**